<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Two Famous Computer Scientists</string>
    <string name="gosling">James Arthur Gosling</string>
    <string name="lee">Sir Timothy John Berners-Lee</string>
    <string name="goslingtxt">        James Arthur Gosling, OC (born May 19, 1955) is a Canadian computer scientist, best known as the father of the Java programming language.\n\nIn 1977, Gosling received a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science from the University of Calgary. \n\nIn 1983, he earned a Ph.D in Computer Science from Carnegie Mellon University, supervised by Bob Sproull.\n\nWhile working towards his doctorate, he wrote a version of Emacs called Gosling Emacs (Gosmacs), and before joining Sun Microsystems he built a multi-processor version of Unix 
        while at Carnegie Mellon University, as well as several compilers and mail systems.\n\nBetween 1984 and 2010, Gosling was with Sun Microsystems.\n\nOn April 2, 2010, Gosling left Sun Microsystems which had recently been acquired by the Oracle Corporation. 
\n\nOn March 28, 2011, James Gosling announced on his blog that he had been hired by Google. Five months later, he announced that he joined a startup called Liquid Robotics.\n\nGosling is listed as an advisor at the Scala company Typesafe Inc. and Strategic Advisor for Eucalyptus.\n\nGosling is generally credited with having invented the Java programming language in 1994. He created the original design of Java and implemented the language\'s original compiler and virtual machine. \n\nFor his achievement he was elected to Foreign Associate member of the United States National Academy of Engineering.</string>
    <string name="leetxt">Sir Timothy John \"Tim\" Berners-Lee, OM, KBE, FRS, FREng, FRSA, DFBCS (born 8 June 1955), also known as \"TimBL,\" is a British computer scientist, 
        best known as the inventor of the World Wide Web.\n\n He made a proposal for an information management system in March 1989, and he implemented the first successful communication between a 
         Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) client and server via the Internet sometime around mid November.\n\nBerners-Lee is the director of the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C), which oversees the Web\'s continued development. 
He is also the founder of the World Wide Web Foundation, and is a senior researcher and holder of the Founders Chair at the MIT Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Laboratory (CSAIL).\n\n He is a director of the Web Science Research Initiative (WSRI), and a member of the advisory board of the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence.\n\nIn 2004, Berners-Lee was knighted by Queen Elizabeth II for his pioneering work.\n\n In April 2009, he was elected a foreign associate of the United States National Academy of Sciences.\n\n He was honoured as the \"Inventor of the World Wide Web\" during the 2012 Summer Olympics opening ceremony, in which he appeared in person, working with a vintage NeXT Computer at the London Olympic Stadium.\n\n He tweeted \"This is for everyone\", which was instantly spelled out in LCD lights attached to the chairs of the 80,000 people in the audience.</string>

</resources>